we're put in that same situation
that a lot of other people are too you
know we have depression we have anxiety
we have situations
um where a lot of pressure is put on our
shoulders and where victory seems like
it's the only option and there's a lot
of times in life where it seems like you
have no choice
but to just
either keep going or to give up and i
find those situations for me i focus on
myself and i focus on just being a
little bit better as an individual a
little bit better as andrew kirka and i
turn out to be a better ski racer in the
process i turned out to be a better
person by the end and i think that's
always a really important thing to focus
on especially when it comes to sport
especially when it comes to competing
clean
you